Things sure have changed. Not everyone
事情肯定已經改變。不是每個人
believes it, but the bad guys went good.
相信這一點，但是壞傢伙進展不錯。
And we cannot wait for society to
我們等不及社會
welcome us with open arms. Aren't you a
歡迎我們張開雙臂。你不是嗎
notorious criminal? Yes. No. Maybe.
臭名昭著的罪犯？是的。不，也許。
Sorry. Sorry. Nerves. It hasn't been
對不起。對不起。神經。不是
easy with a reputation like ours. You
像我們這樣的聲譽輕鬆。你
want to work at a bank? Why not? Some of
想在銀行工作嗎？為什麼不呢？其中一些
my best memories are at banks. You
我最好的回憶是在銀行。你
robbed us three times. Duh. That was
搶走了我們三遍。du。那是
this bank.
這家銀行。
How are we supposed to get a fresh start
我們應該如何重新開始
if no one will trust us? I'm keeping my
如果沒有人會信任我們？我保留我的
eye on you guys. What? What was that? I
看著你們。什麼？那是什麼？我
panicked. Okay, I'm a panicer.
驚慌失措。好吧，我是一個狂歡者。
The name's Kitty and these are my
這個名字的小貓，這些是我的
associates. So, you're like the bad
同事。所以，你就像壞的
girl. We need the bad guys for the
女孩。我們需要壞人
biggest heist in history. Maybe you
歷史上最大的搶劫。也許你
don't keep up with the news, but we're
不要跟上新聞，但我們
good now. I'm not exactly asking.
現在好。我並不是完全問。
Don't tell me you guys are bad again.
不要告訴我你們再次很糟糕。
No, we're being set up. We need to show
不，我們正在設置。我們需要顯示
the world we're good. So, we're going to
我們的世界很好。所以，我們要
sabotage him.
破壞他。
All right, Mr. Master of Disguise,
好的，偽裝大師先生，
you're up. I promise to play you
你起來了。我保證會扮演你
respectfully. My
尊敬。我的
flowers, do your thing. I'll be your
花，做你的事。我是你的
hacker today. Snake, we're going to need
今天黑客。蛇，我們需要
some extra muscle. I'm late for a
一些額外的肌肉。我遲到了
venyasa. Venyasa. You think I got this
Vinyasa。Vinyasa。你以為我知道了
body by sitting around watching TV? And
坐在看電視周圍的身體？和
then we just have to tear them apart
那我們只需要將它們拆開
limb by limb until all they can remember
四肢肢體直到他們記得
is pain.
是痛苦。
Wow. Okay. I was going to say stop him,
哇。好的。我要說阻止他，
but sure. If there's time, we can do the
但可以肯定。如果有時間，我們可以做
limb thing.
肢體的東西。
First time for everything, right?
第一次做一切，對吧？
Pull us up, snake
拉我們，蛇
vignasa,
vignasa，
baby. Come on.
嬰兒。快點。
Are you kidding me? Lefty loosey, righty
你在開玩笑吧？左撇子，對
tighty.
緊身。
Oh, right.
哦，對。
You're not nervous, right? Cuz we know
你不緊張，對嗎？因為我們知道
what happens when you're nervous, buddy.
當你緊張時會發生什麼，哥們。
I'm sorry. What? No. No. No.
對不起。什麼？編號。
No. Help me. Stay with me, B. Stay with
不，幫我。和我在一起，B。留
me.
我。
Racing is my dream.
賽車是我的夢想。
I could race in the Grand Prix and I
我可以參加大獎賽和我
could win. You'll get your chance to
可以贏。您將有機會
race someday. He is the fourtime Grand
有一天。他是四個盛大的
Prix champion.
冠軍冠軍。
It's Ed's car.
這是埃德的車。
This is unhealthy.
這是不健康的。
Stop. Get out of my car. Okay. And
停止。下車。好的。和
[Applause]
[掌聲]
your arms like a noodle. I'm over here.
你的手臂像麵條。我在這裡。
There's your arm.
有你的手臂。
It's not broken. No driving for a few
它沒有打破。沒有開車
weeks. Weeks. I have an idea. We look
幾週。幾週。我有一個主意。我們看
alike. I could take your place. Also,
也一樣。我可以代替你。還，
you give me half the prize money or
你給我一半的獎金或
there's no deal. All right, deal. I
沒有交易。好的，交易。我
can't believe I'm going to drive in the
不敢相信我會開車去
Grand Prix.
大獎賽。
Neither can I.
也不能。
Welcome to the Grand Prix. I must be
歡迎來到大獎賽。我一定是
dreaming.
做夢。
Nice driving.
不錯的駕駛。
Be careful. One mistake can cost you.
當心。一個錯誤可能會花費您。
That was totally a threat. I still
那完全是一個威脅。我還是
really want his autograph, though.
不過，真的想要他的簽名。
He's completely lost control.
他完全失去了控制。
Maybe my dream should have stayed a
也許我的夢想應該留下
dream. I believe in you, Ed. You've got
夢。我相信你，埃德。你有
this.
這。
Watch this. This is unbelievable.
看這個。這是令人難以置信的。
[Music]
[音樂]
Wa. Yeah. Wa.
圓圈。是的。圓圈。
Are you ready to get pumped up?
您準備好被抽水了嗎？
Hello everyone. I have big news. I found
大家好。我有大新聞。我找到了
Smurf Village. I'm one step closer to
藍精靈村。我離我很近
total evil
完全邪惡
dominance. Lame. You're all lame.
主導地位。瘸。你們都la腳。
Hit it, papa.
打，爸爸。
[Music]
[音樂]
I
我
think
思考
it feel like a friend.
感覺就像是朋友。
What the smurf?
什麼藍精靈？
No, I think I just smurfed my pants.
不，我想我只是用褲子。
Code blue
代碼藍色
from Paramount Pictures. We got to
從派拉蒙圖片。我們必須去
rescue Papa. Let me guess. Papa Smurf's
救援爸爸。讓我猜。爸爸藍精靈的
in trouble.
遇到麻煩。
We are storming Rosamel's castle and we
我們正在衝進羅莎梅爾的城堡，我們
take no prisoners except for Papa. We'll
除了爸爸以外，沒有囚犯。出色地
make sure and grab him. Everybody know
確保並抓住他。大家都知道
the game to do. We're going to need help
遊戲要做。我們需要幫助
from
從
the Snood Poots. Snutder Poots.
snod po。Snutder Pots。
Hey, what are they saying?
嘿，他們在說什麼？
this July. If we don't stop these
今年七月。如果我們不停止這些
wizards,
巫師，
it'll mean the end of the universe.
這意味著宇宙的末尾。
Sound effect. Smurf, can you back off?
聲音效果。藍精靈，你能退縮嗎？
Let's go smurf that wizard up. Oh, yeah.
讓我們去那個嚮導的藍精靈。哦，是的。
Get ready. Race for impact for an
準備。競爭一場影響力的影響
adventure that will blow you away. Come
冒險會讓您震驚。來
on.
在。
What the Smurf?
什麼藍精靈？
Hold on, you little Smurf.
等等，你小藍精靈。
We're here to save everything. Goodbye,
我們在這裡保存一切。再見，
Smurfves. Forever.
藍精靈。永遠。
Now that's what I call a banger. Smurfs
現在，這就是我所說的爆炸。藍精靈
featuring new music by Rihanna and more.
由蕾哈娜（Rihanna）等新音樂節目。
It's a new day. We're taking a trip to
這是新的一天。我們正在旅行
spend the week with my grandma.
和我奶奶一起度過一周。
Buckle up, Gabby Catch. It's time to go.
係好，Gabby Catch。是時候去了。
Here we go.
開始了。
Do you want to come to San Francisco
你想來舊金山嗎
with us? Let's do it.
和我們在一起？我們開始做吧。
We're here.
我們在這裡。
The
這
dollhouse. Not over dramatic. I think
娃娃屋。沒有過分戲劇性。我認為
we're moving.
我們正在搬家。
Everyone clean left. The other left.
每個人都很乾淨。另一個左。
Baby box. I'm learning so much today.
嬰兒盒。我今天學到了很多。
Molina. Mommy will be right back. Who is
莫利納。媽媽會馬上回來。誰是
that?
那？
What do we have here? Vera wondered
我們在這裡有什麼？維拉想知道
aloud as a man in the street yelled at
大聲大聲喊著
her. Seriously, lady, what is wrong with
她。說真的，女士，怎麼了
you?
你？
This dollhouse will complete my cat
這個玩具屋將完成我的貓
collection. Add to cart. No, girl. Bye.
收藏。添加到購物車。不，女孩。再見。
It's time to get tiny. Let's get this
現在該變得很小了。讓我們得到這個
dollhouse back. We're leaving the
娃娃屋回來。我們要離開
planet. Oh, this is awesome. You can
行星。哦，這太棒了。你可以
come.
來。
My hair, my tushy, my fashion. Oh, wait.
我的頭髮，我的頭髮，我的時尚。哦，等等。
Can I scratch that? I look fabulous.
我可以刮擦嗎？我看起來很棒。
[Music]
[音樂]
I have a feeling we're going to need
我有一種我們需要的
backup. What's wrong? This is a
備份。怎麼了？這是一個
dollhouse problem.
娃娃屋問題。
Oops. Looks like cakey got faked.
糟糕。看起來蛋糕是偽造的。
Here we go. Marina, bring me my yoga
開始了。碼頭，給我瑜伽
mat.
墊。
Oh, pulling out the wishbone. You are
哦，拔出叉骨。你是
really trying to destroy the universe
真的試圖摧毀宇宙
right now, aren't
現在，不是
[Music]
[音樂]
you? Help.
你？幫助。
Toothless. It's okay. I won't hurt you.
無牙。沒關係。我不會傷害你。
Everything we know about
我們知道的一切
dragons is wrong.
龍是錯誤的。
The reign of the dragons. It's right
龍的統治。是的
here, right now.
現在，現在。
I'm the first Viking
我是第一個維京人
who wouldn't kill a dragon. First to
誰不會殺死龍。首先
ride one, though.
不過，騎一個。
All right, bud. You ready?
好吧，芽。你準備好了嗎？
[Applause]
[掌聲]
[Music]
[音樂]
Come on. Come on. Yeah. Look at
快點。快點。是的。看
us. My fault.
我們。我的錯。
You have something none of us
你們沒有我們的東西
Come on, bud.
來吧，芽。
[Music]
[音樂]
Watch out.
提防。
[Music]
[音樂]
Hey, Magic Mirror. Who's the fairest of
嘿，魔術鏡。誰是最公平的
them all? Why, Shrek, of course.
商場？為什麼，史瑞克，當然。
Ew, Dad. Woohoo! Mama light. Who's
EW，爸爸。哇！媽媽光。誰是
making this stuff? Not me.
做這個東西？不是我。
Whoa.
哇。
Shrek 5 starring Mike Myers, Eddie
史瑞克5由邁克·邁爾斯（Mike Myers）主演的埃迪（Eddie）
Murphy, Cameron Diaz, and Zandea. Oh,
墨菲，卡梅倫·迪亞茲（Cameron Diaz）和Zandea。哦，
damn. Only in theaters Christmas 2026.
該死。僅在劇院2026年。